uppfly.com 2015-11-05

# Seopower Privacy Policy – Point to Mark While Submitting Bookmarking

seopower.in is founded on the principles of helping people to discover new information by enabling them to share what they find interesting with one another. We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. By visiting this website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers seopower’s treatment of personal information that gathers when you are on this website and when you use services of this website. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that does not control, or to an individual that does not employ or manage.

We only collect personal information that is significant to the purpose of our website, which is to enable users to discover and share information with one another. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not procedure this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our seopower users:-

**1.Information you provide to us: -** ** **   
We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. 

**User Profile** :   
: To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration; we enable you to provide additional information. In addition, you may choose to include photos of yourself in your profile. As indicated below, in the section titled "Sharing Your Information", you can control how your information is displayed and used.

**2\. Automatic Information:** ** **  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you cooperate with us. Its authorized agents routinely record and receive certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address. This website uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.
